(Penny:)How about we just have
a little quiet time now?
(Sheldon:)All right.
[SHELDON WHIMPERS]
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry.
I'm finding your reckless nonchalance...
(Sheldon:)...regarding the check-engine light
to be very troubling.
(Penny(Pulling over):)Get out.
(Sheldon:)I have to tell you that while I do have
a theoretical understanding...
...of an internal-combustion engine...
(Sheldon:)...I'm not sure
I'm capable of performing diagnostics.
I said, "Get out."
(Sheldon:)Okay, I'll give it a shot.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Leonard, there you are.
(Sheldon:)I'm ready to go home.
(Leonard:)I just got here.
(Sheldon:)Good. Perfect timing.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I told you, I only have access
to the free-electron laser at night.